A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Developing Countries Program, Office Files of Anne C. Kubisch FA524
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, Developing Countries Program, Office Files of Anne C. Kubisch
1985-1987
Rockefeller Archive Center
Kubisch, Anne C.
Ford Foundation
FA524
1.31 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Scope and Contents
Correspondence
Arrangement
Chronological
Biographical / Historical
Anne C. Kubisch is a foundation executive who worked for several years at the Ford Foundation. In 1985, she joined the Foundation as an Assistant Program Officer in the Developing Country Programs. She then moved from the larger Developing Country Programs to its specific West Africa Program as Assistant Representative and Program Officer. Later, she moved to the Urban Poverty Program where she worked as a Program Officer before being appointed Deputy Director.
After leaving the Ford Foundation in 1994, Kubisch became Director for the Roundtable on Community Change at The Aspen Institute. In 2003, she became President and CEO of the Ford Family Foundation (TFFF).
Kubisch earned a B.A. in English from Tufts University and a master's degree in public policy from the Princeton University School of Public and International Affairs. Prior to joining the Ford Foundation, she worked as a Staff Assistant to David Rockefeller.
- Chronological Correspondence Files, 1985-1987; I
  - 1985 Chronological Correspondence (1 of 4), 1985 February-March (Box 1)
  - 1985 Chronological Correspondence (2 of 4), 1985 April-May (Box 1)
  - 1985 Chronological Correspondence (3 of 4), 1985 June-September (Box 1)
  - 1985 Chronological Correspondence (4 of 4), 1985 October-December (Box 1)
  - 1986 Chronological Correspondence (1 of 3), 1986 January-March (Box 1)
  - 1986 Chronological Correspondence (2 of 3), 1986 April-July (Box 1)
  - 1986 Chronological Correspondence (3 of 3), 1986 August-December (Box 1)
  - 1987 Chronological Correspondence (1 of 4), 1987 January-April (Box 1)
  - 1987 Chronological Correspondence (2 of 4), 1987 May-July (Box 1)
  - 1987 Chronological Correspondence (3 of 4), 1987 August (Box 1)
  - 1987 Chronological Correspondence, Unsorted (4 of 4), 1987 January-October (Box 1)